Rouichi Ouryou
Mr. Ouryou, your daughter
is here to see you again.
王陵さん　また娘さんがお見舞いに来てくださったわよ
Isn't that nice?
よかったですね
I'm sorry, but your father knows
you're here and is happy to see you, too.
ごめんなさいね
お父さんもちゃんと分かってて 喜んでくださってますから
So please don't get discouraged.
気を落とさないでくださいね
Yes, of course.
ええ　もちろん
That's a lie. Everyone here is the same.
嘘だ　ここにいる人々の全てがそうだ
They don't notice anything.
They don't say anything.
何も気付かず 何も語らず そして何も考えない
And they don't think anything.
They are merely a shell
of their former selves and soon
ただの抜け殻のように生きて やがて
they will disappear like the melting snow.
雪が解けるように消えていく
This epidemic leads
innocent people to their deaths...
罪なき人々を死に至らしめる伝染病
...and yet, its pathogen will never be eradicated.
でも　この病原菌が根絶されることはない
This is a disease called serenity...
これは安らぎという名の病
...a form of death that people have wished for.
人々が望んだ死の形
My head is overflowing with thoughts
I can't allow anyone to know about
I've strayed into a world void of even mistakes
It's being rubbed in so deep it's hard to believe
This "world" that holds
only what the eye can see
Can I flush out the truth?
Plastic Tac Tic,
no one can go crazy anymore
You, too, are in a plastic beautiful world
In a world with too much beauty,
for some reason I can't see the light
My bursting heart is an eternal reflection
Secret remains for you
Don't expose these false colors and futures
fake's plastic world
keep it secret motion
本字幕由诸神字幕组制作 更多字幕欢迎访问http://www.kamigami.org
翻译:草泥马 TMR@10 校对:西西   后期:时末
#07 Symbolism of Bletilla Striata
This is...
Don't tell me...
They first dismembered
and cut open the body,
これって… まさか…
and then they used plastination
to turn it into a human specimen.
Then they brought it right into
the middle of town and displayed it...
バラバラに切り開いた遺体をプラスティネーションで標本にして
I'm taking you off this case, Kogami.
そいつを街のど真ん中に飾りつけてくれたわけよ
What?
Why... Gino?
今回の捜査から外れてもらうぞ　狡噛
I can't allow a detective who can't
put aside his preconceived notions
何でだ　ギノ
to be a part of the initial investigation.
余計な先入観にとらわれた刑事を初動捜査に加えるわけにはいかない
Even so...
そんな…でもまだ標本事件と一緒ってわけじゃ…
But we still don't know if this is
connected to the Specimen Case.
Ah!
So I'm on standby at my quarters, right?
宿舎で待機だな
That's right.
そうだ
Inspector Tsunemori.
常守監視官
Y-Yes!
はっ　はい
It seems that you're
aware of the circumstances.
どうやら事情は知っている様子だし
Watch Kogami at all times to make
sure that he won't do anything stupid.
狡噛が妙なことをしでかさないよう 付きっきりで監視しろ
That's your job in this case.
それが今回の 君の仕事だ
I'll summarize the case.
整理する
The dismembered body found in
a park in Daikanyama, Shibuya Ward,
渋谷区代官山の公園で発見されたバラバラ死体は
belonged to Satsuki Kuzuhara,
who was a student
葛原沙月
全寮制の女子高等教育機関桜霜学園の生徒だ
at Ousou Academy, a higher
education girls boarding school.
She went missing a week ago.
１週間前から行方不明になっていた
Hey, Ousou Academy is...
おい　「桜霜学園」って
...where Kouzaburou Touma, the suspect
in the Specimen Case, worked...
標本事件の容疑者 藤間幸三郎の勤務先
...right?
でしたよね
The body was eroded
by a special kind of chemical,
遺体は特殊な薬剤に浸食され タンパク質がプラスチック状に変質
and the protein
was converted into plastic form.
Analysis confirmed that
the chemical used in this case
分析の結果　これは３年前の事件で使われた薬品と同一であることが判明した
was the same one that was
used in the case three years ago.
It's true that these cases more
than likely share the same culprit.
確かに同一犯の可能性は高い
So after three years, the mysterious
homicidal maniac has come back, huh?
謎の殺人鬼が３年ぶりにカムバックってわけか
Gino! Was it really okay
to remove Ko from the case?
ギノさーん ホントにコウちゃん 外してよかったんすか
He's been investigating the
Specimen Case all this time, right?
あの人標本事件の調査って続行してたでしょ
He might have been able to
find some new leads on the case.
何か新しい手掛かりとかつかんでたかも
I've read his report.
やつの報告書には目を通してある
It's completely delusional.
あれは　ただの妄想の羅列だ
You're going too far...
やり過ぎですよ 狡噛さん
Mr. Kogami.
Whoa!
You've got sparring set to the highest level!
スパーリング最高レベルに設定してあるじゃないですか
Are you really human, Mr. Kogami?
本当に人間ですか　狡噛さん
Yeah, but I still get knocked
unconscious if I get hit by a Paralyzer.
ああ　それでもパラライザーで撃たれれば気絶する
I'm just a weak human.
ただのやわな人間だ
I bet the Property Management Division
is gonna scold you for this.
後で絶対に管財課から怒られますよ
It's because their
system is a piece of crap.
ダサ過ぎんだよこのシステムが
俺の顔に何か付いてるのか
Is there something on my face?
No, there isn't!
いや　別に…
ドミネーターほど強力な武器が支給されるのに
You get provided with a powerful
weapon like the Dominator.
ここまで過剰な戦闘訓練が必要なんですか
Do you really have to engage
in this much combat training?
Yeah, I do.
必要だ
強くて優れた武器を扱うからこそ その使い手はより強くタフでなきゃいけない
Especially because the
weapon is powerful and superior,
its user has to be stronger and tougher.
It's me who kills
a person, not the Dominator.
相手を殺すのはドミネーターじゃなく この俺だと…
In order to keep that in mind,
それを肝に銘じておくためにも ここにちゃんと痛みを感じておかないとな
I have to feel the pain here.
Is that a lesson for me?
それって　私に対する教訓ですか
I don't wanna be in a situation
where you have to fire the Dominator.
あんたにドミネーターを撃たせるような状況は 願い下げだぜ
So, what do you want?
で　何の用だ
Before that, please wipe off your
sweat with a towel and put a shirt on!
その前にタオルで汗拭いて服をちゃんと着てください
About the unsolved case,
未解決事件
MWPSB Special Case 102...
公安局 広域重要指定事件１０２について
I apologize for secretly checking
into it as if I was snooping.
こっそり　のぞき見するみたいに調べたのは謝ります
Why do you apologize?
なぜ謝る
You aren't angry with me?
怒ってないんですか
Why do I have to get angry?
どうして俺が怒らなきゃいけないんだ
About a past murder case in
which one of my subordinates got killed?
過去の部下を殺された事件のことで
About the case that hasn't
been solved even after three years?
３年もたつのに解決できてない事件のことで
I wouldn't get angry
about those things. If I did,
怒らないさ
俺が怒るとすれば
my anger would
solely be directed at myself.
その対象は自分自身以外あり得ない
In that murder case, I wasn't even able
to get close to finding the mastermind
あの事件　藤間幸三郎の背後で糸を引いていた黒幕に
who was pulling the
strings behind Kouzaburou Touma.
俺はかすることすらできなかった
Do you think that the
same guy is involved in this case?
今回の事件も同じ人物が関与していると
I don't know yet.
まだ分からない ただの手の込んだだけの模倣犯という可能性もある
It's still possible that this is
just an elaborate copycat crime.
But there's no mistake
that it's worth looking into.
だが　調べる価値があるのは間違いない
You've been taken off this case.
捜査から外されちゃいましたね
That's okay.
別にいいさ
I don't wanna cause Gino too much trouble.
あんまりギノを困らせてもな
What?
I'm saying, there's a way of going about things.
やり方はあるってことだよ
We can find a good pretext to create
a situation where they'd need us back.
うまい口実を見つけて 俺たちが戻らざるを得ない状況を作り出せばいい
Is there such a way?
そんな方法が
There is. Just wait and see.
あるさ　まあ見てろ
What kind of person was Enforcer Sasayama?
佐々山執行官ってどんな人だったんですか
He was a piece of work.
くそ野郎だった
Huh?
はあ
He was a womanizer.
女好きでね
Who knows how often
Karanomori and Kunizuka
唐之杜や六合塚なんて何度尻を触られたことか
had their butts grabbed by him...
Even though he got slugged every time,
he never seemed to learn his lesson.
そのたびにぶん殴られるのに まったく 懲りる様子がなかったな
Also, he had a short temper.
あと短気だった
Once he got upset,
there was nothing anyone could do.
一度火が付くと手が付けられなくてな
One day, he went to the house of
a guy who got flagged by a Hue check.
あるとき 色相チェックに引っ掛かった容疑者宅に踏み込むと
When he stepped inside, this guy was
on top of a woman he had kidnapped.
まさにさらった女性にのしかかってるところだった
Sasayama almost killed this guy.
佐々山はその男を危うく殺しかけた
Since I was an Inspector at
the time, I stopped him,
当時俺は監視官だったから 一応止めたが
but deep down, I thought
that he was an amusing guy...
内心楽しいやつだと思ってた
That womanizing, violent bastard
was truly an amusing guy.
女好きで凶暴で 実に楽しいくそ野郎だと…
At the very least,
I never expected he'd die that way.
少なくとも　あんな死に方をするような男じゃなかった
Did you see the picture of his body?
死体の写真は見たか
Yes.
はい
His body was placed underneath
a Holographic illumination.
死体はホログラフ·イルミネーションの裏側に配置されていた
Yes...
はい…
Do you know what
kind of illumination it was?
イルミネーションの内容は知ってるか
No, I don't.
いいえ　そこまでは
It was an ad by a pharmaceutical company.
薬品会社の広告だった
"Safe stress care. Taking you
to a world without suffering."
安全なストレスケア 苦しみのない世界へ
Analysis showed that before
Sasayama was turned into a specimen,
佐々山は標本化される前
he was dismembered while he was still alive.
生きたまま解体されたことが 分析で判明した
It was like the culprit was sending a message...
犯人のメッセージみたいだったよ
"Life is nothing but suffering."
「苦しいだけが人生だ」って
I wanted the guy who did that to
Sasayama to meet the same end...
それをしでかしたやつを同じ目に遭わせてやりたいと
Once I started feeling that way,
いつからかそんなふうに思うようになった時点で
my career as an Inspector was over.
監視官としての俺はもう終わってた
Do you have any regrets?
後悔はありませんか
I don't regret my actions.
自分の行動に後悔はない
But the thing is...
the case is still unsolved.
問題は　未解決なこと
That's the only problem.
この一点に尽きる
The accomplice who helped
Kouzaburou Touma three years ago...
３年前　藤間幸三郎に手を貸した共犯者
Are there any leads that we can still use?
今でも使えそうな手掛かりは 何かありますか
Yeah.
There's a picture that Sasayama took...
佐々山が撮った写真がある
...though it's pretty blurry.
ひどくピンぼけだがな
It was saved on the
terminal that Sasayama used.
佐々山の使ってた端末に保存されていた
This man... Did you
find out what his name is?
この男…名前とかは
The picture's filename was..."Makishima."
画像ファイルのタイトルは…「マキシマ」だった
The body was Satsuki Kuzuhara's.
死体は葛原沙月さんだった
Yeah, I heard.
らしいね
Yoshika has been absent
from school since yesterday.
葦歌ちゃんが昨日から欠席してる
Yeah, I heard.
らしいね
Hey, listen to me seriously.
ねえ ちょっと真面目に聞いてよ
I am listening.
聞いてるよ
It's not just Okubo.
大久保さんだけじゃない Ｂ組の山口昌美も欠席が続いてるってさ
I heard that Masami Yamaguchi in
Class B has been absent, too.
Something bad is probably
going on in this academy.
たぶん　この学園でよくないことが起きている
So?
それで
"So"?
「それで」って
I wouldn't get near something bad from the start.
よくないことには最初から近づかない 噂話もしない
I wouldn't gossip, either.
What're you saying?
何それ…
I feel like a careless action could
really put us in serious danger.
うかつに動くと 本当に危ない気がする
We've been friends with
Yoshika since we were kids, you know.
葦歌ちゃん 私たちの幼なじみじゃない
Rikako Ouryou.
王陵璃華子
What?
Okubo was really crazy about her, right?
大久保さん かなり入れ揚げてたんでしょ
Rikako seemed to show
some interest in her as well.
向こうも案外 まんざらでもなかった様子だし
If you ask her, she might know something.
聞いてみたら何か知ってるかもよ
Yeah...
うん…
There's this quote from
Kierkegaard that my father liked.
父が好きだったキルケゴールの言葉よ
"Because man is superior to animals,
「人間は動物より勝っているからこそ
in other words,
because man is the self, and spirit,
言い換えれば　人間は自己であり精神であるからこそ
man can be in despair."
絶望することができるのである」
Unless you know despair,
you cannot know hope.
絶望を知らなければ希望もない
My father used dismembered bodies
as the subject of many of his drawings.
父の絵の題材にバラバラの人体が多いのは
That's because they symbolize
the contradictory nature of the self.
自己に抱えた矛盾の象徴なのよ
I had great respect for my father.
私は父を尊敬していた
He was aware of his obligation as an artist
芸術家としての義務を自覚して
and continued to focus intently on
using his creations to enlighten people.
啓蒙としての創作姿勢にこだわり続けたあの人は
I think even now that
he was indeed a great artist.
本当に素晴らしい絵描きだったと今でも思ってるわ
Especially because of that,
だからね　その務めを途中で放棄してしまったことがことさらに許せないの
I really can't forgive him for
abandoning that duty halfway through.
Yesterday, my father passed away.
昨日ね　父が亡くなったの
He's been as good as dead for a while,
もうとっくに死んだも同然の人だったけど
but finally even his heart gave in.
とうとう心臓まで本当に止まっちゃった
But I'm okay.
でも大丈夫
I'm not sad.
悲しくなんかないわ
I, his daughter, will carry out my
father's duty together with you guys.
父の務めは　娘の私があなたたちと一緒に果たしていくのよ
Don't you think that's wonderful? It's exciting...
すてきだと思わない？
ドキドキするよね
...right, Yoshika?
葦歌さん
Eustress deficiency cerebral infarction.
ユーストレス欠乏性脳梗塞
Well, that's not the illness's official name.
まあ 公認の病名ではありません
It is said to be the real cause of
most deaths that are declared as
原因不明の心不全という形で処理されている死因のおおかたは
"heart failure from unknown cause."
実は　この症例に該当するといわれています
I've heard of it. They say that it's
a side effect of excessive stress care.
聞いたことはある
過度のストレスケアによる弊害だそうだが…
For some time, it's been understood
that moderate stress has beneficial effects.
かねてより適度のストレスは免疫活動を活性化させるなど
For example,
it stimulates the immune system.
好ましい効果もあるとされてきた
As they say, it's a motivation in your life.
いわゆる 人生の張り合い
You can even call it a reason for living.
生きがいと言い直してもいい
However, once Psycho-Pass
checks became routine,
ところが　サイコパス診断が恒常化してしまった結果
people's sense of stress
has been numbed so much that
ストレスの感覚がまひし過ぎて
patients who can't even recognize
stimulation itself started appearing.
刺激そのものを認識できなくなる患者が出てきた
Once that happens,
they're the same as living corpses.
こうなると　生ける屍も同然です
Soon their autonomic nervous
system stops functioning on its own
やがては自律神経そのものが自らの機能を見失い
and their vital functions shut down.
生命活動を維持できなくなる
That's very sad.
嘆かわしい限りだな
So humans now care for
themselves to the point that
人は自らをいたわるあまり
they've actually regressed
as a living being, huh?
生物としてはむしろ 退化してしまったわけか
The fact of the matter is,
実はね　これだけ医療体制が発展したにもかかわらず
as much as our medical
system has advanced,
statistically, the average
lifespan is actually decreasing.
統計上の平均寿命はむしろ 短くなる傾向にあるんですよ
Well, this data will probably
never be made public, though.
まあ　決して公にはならないデータでしょうが
That's not surprising.
当然だな
In this era, everything that could be
called a reason for living has died out.
この時代 生きがいと呼び得るものは全て枯れ果ててしまった
No one tries to talk seriously about
what life should be like anymore.
命の在り方を誰も真面目に語ろうとしなくなった
The father of Rikako Ouryou,
the girl I mentioned earlier,
くだんの王陵璃華子の父親もね
had eustress deficiency as well.
まさにそのユーストレス欠乏症患者だったんです
Rouichi Ouryou...
王陵牢一
At some point,
he was a predominant illustrator.
ある時期一世を風靡したイラストレーターです
Haven't you heard of him?
ご存じありませんか？
Unfortunately, I don't have
much knowledge of the art world.
あいにくと美術の世界には造詣がなくてね
He was a genius in drawing cruel,
vivid nightmares using girls' bodies as motifs.
少女の肉体をモチーフに 残虐で生々しい悪夢を描き出す天才でした
However, he himself was
a man of quite strict morality.
ところが　本人は至って生真面目なモラリストでね
Well, it's not uncommon for there to
be a disconnect between the creator and
まあ　作品のイメージと制作者の実態が乖離しているのは珍しくもない話ですが
the impression their creations give.
But in Rouichi's case,
there was a firm ideology there.
牢一の場合にはそこに確たる理念があった
According to him,
いわく　人間は心の暗部 内に秘めた残虐性を正しく自覚することで
by becoming firmly aware of the cruelty
that's hiding in the dark depths of
the human heart, humans can foster
the common sense,
ability to reason, and goodwill
それを律する良識と理性、善意を培うことができると…
that can control that cruelty.
He defined his creation activities
as enlightening people about that.
彼はそのための啓発として自らの創作活動を定義づけていた
From what you say,
he sounds like quite the saint.
聞くかぎりではとんだ聖人君主ではないか
However, the spread of
Psycho-Pass assessments
しかし　サイコパス判定の普及が彼の自認する役目を終わらせた
ended this role that
he had decided for himself.
People don't have to control
themselves anymore. Instead,
人は自らを律するまでもなく
they can now maintain their mental
health through machine assessments.
機械による計測で心の健康を保てるようになった
I heard... that Rouichi
welcomed this technology.
牢一はね　このテクノロジーを歓迎したそうです
Whatever the means was,
方法はどうあれ 彼が理想とした人の心の健やかなる形は実現した
his ideal of humans having a healthy
and sound mind has been realized.
As a result, though, his mission had
ended and his life lost its meaning.
その結果として自らの使命が完了し
その人生は無価値なものになったわけですが…
I'm surprised.
驚きだな　芸術家などというのは総じて俗物だと思っていたが…
I thought all artists were the same,
concerned only with fame and wealth.
Well, he too probably had inner conflicts.
まあ　心には葛藤もあったでしょうが
But in order to solve them,
牢一はその解消に早速先端技術である各種のストレスケアを活用した
he used all sorts of
state-of-the-art stress care methods.
His daughter Rikako tells me
that he was so dependent on them
その依存ぶりは耽溺と言っていいほどだったと
that you could call it an addiction.
娘の璃華子は語ってます
As a result,
その結果　ベッドから起き上がることもない 生きた死体に成り果てたと…
he became a living corpse who
couldn't even sit up on the bed, huh?
Since she loved her father so much,
父を慕う娘からしてみれば 許し難い話でしょうね
I bet she felt it was unforgivable.
It's as if Rouichi Ouryou was killed twice.
王陵牢一は二度殺されたようなものです
First his talent was killed
by science and technology.
まずは科学技術によって才能を殺され
And then, his soul was killed by society.
そして社会によって魂を殺された
In short, you mean this girl is committing
crimes to get revenge for her father?
つまり　その少女の犯行の動機は父親の復讐かね？
Well, I don't know.
さて　どうでしょう？
I hope she finds some
meaning beyond revenge, though.
願わくば　さらに向こう側の意義を見いだしてほしいものですが…
Choe Gu-Sung?
チェ·グソン？
That was quick.
お早いお出ましで
In any case, I wonder how
それにしても槙島先生はどうして学園内にこんな場所があるなんて知っていたのかしら？
Mr. Makishima knew that there
was a place like this inside the academy.
It seems that this used to be a
generator room for a boiler for recyclables,
もともとはリサイクルボイラーの発電室だったのが
but when it was closed for renovations,
it also disappeared from the blueprints.
改装で閉鎖されたとき 図面からも抜け落ちたみたいで
How slipshod, huh?
ずさんなもんです
So where's the chemical?
それで　薬の方は？
It's over there.
そちらに
Deliveries aren't usually my thing,
別に俺の専門は荷運びじゃないんですがね
but the payment this time is quite generous.
今回は手当も弾んでもらえてますし
In addition, I get to help out such
a cute young lady like yourself.
こんなカワイイお嬢さんのお手伝いってんなら
So, I hardly have reason to complain.
まあ　文句をつける筋合いでもありませんな
Where does Mr. Makishima
get a mysterious thing like this?
こんな不思議なものを 槙島先生はいったいどこから？
He did say that they're leftover
stockpiles from past festivities.
昔仕込んだ祭りの残りとは言ってましたがね
I don't know who made it.
I don't even wanna know.
誰が作ったもんなのかは知らないし 知りたくもないが
The person must've thought
そいつはこの妙ちきりんな薬で特許取ったり商いをしたりするより
that entertaining Mr. Makishima
would be a lot more worthwhile
than getting a patent for
this weird chemical or selling it.
槙島の旦那を楽しませる方がよほど有意義だと思ったんでしょうね
I guess geniuses who use
their talents for the wrong purposes
先生の周囲にはいつも才能の使いどころを間違えた天才が集まってくるのでしょうね
always gather around him.
And you're one of
them, right, Choe Gu-Sung?
あなたもその１人なのでしょう？
チェ·グソン…
I don't know what it is...
何なんですかね
...but when I'm with him, it's like I'm
reliving my childhood or something.
あの人と一緒にいると 童心に帰るっていうか
What mischief should we get
up to in order to surprise society?
どんないたずらを仕掛けて世間をあっと言わせてやるか
My head is filled with those thoughts.
そればっかり夢中になっちまう
I know the feeling.
分かるわ　その気持ち
You guys prepare toys,
あなたたちがおもちゃを用意し
and we, mischievous children,
use those toys to shake up society.
それを使って私たちのようないたずらっ子が世の中を騒がせる
It really is fun, isn't it?
楽しいわよね 本当に
Well, for us, the toy dealers,
まあ　俺らおもちゃ屋は
just enjoying what you
brats do is good enough.
あんたたち悪がきのやることを眺めて楽しむだけで十分です
Yeah. They might be discovering
my second mischief right about now.
そうね そろそろ２つ目のいたずらが見つかる頃合いじゃないかしら
You should pay attention to the news.
ニュースに注目しとくといいわ
Will do.
そうさせてもらいましょう
You always leave before the really
fun stuff begins. It's a shame you miss it.
あなた いつも一番楽しい場面には付き合わずに帰っちゃうのね
もったいないわ
Unfortunately, I don't do too
well around blood and stuff, so...
あいにく 血なまぐさいのは苦手なもんでね
A second one...
２件目か…
If this is really Kouzaburou Touma's
doing, this is the sixth one.
これが藤間幸三郎の犯行なら ６件目ですよ
So, what is it that you wanted
to ask me, Kagami Kawarazaki?
それで私に相談事って何かしら？
川原崎加賀美さん
Yoshika...
葦歌ちゃん…
It's about Okubo.
大久保さんの件なんです
She's been absent from school
for three days in a row, so... uhm...
彼女もう３日続けて欠席してて その…
So you're worried.
You care about your friends.
心配なのね 川原崎さんは友達思いね
We've been friends since childhood.
彼女 私の幼なじみで…
This is...
これは…
Friendship between girls is wonderful, isn't it?
女の子同士の友情ってすてきね
It might be able to become a very exciting motif.
それはそれでモチーフとしてとっても刺激的かも
Uhm...
It might also be a good addition to
my exhibition of Yoshika, don't you think?
葦歌さんを展示するに当たって
そういう志向もいいわよね
A touching reunion with your childhood friend...
幼なじみとの感動の対面
It's an emotionally stirring scene,
isn't it? It really makes me cry.
心揺さぶられる場面よね
本当　泣かせられるわ
I want to reenact this moving scene in
a place where more and more people can see it.
この感動をもっともっと大勢の目に付くところで再現したいってそう思ってしまうのが
Having such thoughts may
indeed be the fate of an artist.
やはり表現者の業かしらね
Looks like the fairy tale died a moment ago
In a hospital ward made of bricks,
I found it hard to sing
Red moon, come out on this foggy night
Now look at me, don't avert your gaze
I was born behind black iron bars
Wish for payback for the evil done
As you wish, I'll give you your justice
Before you destroy and get destroyed
Pay karma's price, and let's go together
Monster without a name
A world where humans' state of mind and the tendency of their
personalities can be quantified. While all sorts of inclinations
are recorded and policed, these measured numbers
used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass."
This story is fiction.
The names of all individuals and organizations that appear in the show
are fictitious and have no relation to those in existence in the real world.